<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<source>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 07:29:12 GMT</lastBuildDate>
            <job>
            <partnerJobId><![CDATA[33]]></partnerJobId>
            <company><![CDATA[Micro Nav]]></company>
            <title><![CDATA[Project Manager]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[
                <p></p>
<p><strong>Purpose of the role</strong></p>
<p>To lead the management of designated Customer and
internal development projects and communicate
project progress to Key Stakeholders and Senior Micro Nav Management in accordance with the requirements of
the Project Plan and Contract.&nbsp; To manage Customer project relations throughout the life of the project.
To manage and deliver projects to approved
schedule and budget and manage bids and
tenders across all lines of business.<strong><br /></strong></p>
<p><strong>Key Duties &amp;
Responsibilities</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Act as Bid Manager for Customer bids and to
assist in the creation of a fully developed quotation document and fully costed project model.</li>
<li>Prepare and present quotation and bid documents,
together with costed project models to senior management for review and approval.</li>
<li>Provide an initial schedule with bid resource
estimates to functional heads to enable them to provide accurate, agreed low level schedules in
return.</li>
<li>Project manage allocated projects to time and
budget expectations.</li>
<li>Create a Project Plan including task breakdown,
schedule and budget.</li>
<li>Liaise with the all lines of business to ensure
accuracy of the data in the Project Plan and to achieve a smooth transition from Sales to
Projects.</li>
<li>Request internal and external resources as
necessary in order to achieve tasks identified as part of a project.</li>
<li>Maintain the schedule in consultation with the
Customer and Micro Nav teams.</li>
<li>Measure progress against the Project Plan,
Schedule and Budget to update as required.</li>
<li>Obtain formal approval within agreed project
criteria for any negative variance to project revenue, profit or schedule.</li>
<li>Identify project slippages and to develop
recovery strategies to allow the planned events to be achieved.</li>
<li>Identify and manage all project risks and to
provide mitigation plans, if necessary, in conjunction with the Customer, and Micro Nav
Management.</li>
<li>Keep all stakeholders aware of any changes to the
project timescale and to agree remedial actions. <br />Assist the Financial Controller in the management of financial instruments and the timely issue
of invoices against agreed project milestones.<strong><br /></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Technical Requirements</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Proficiency in the Microsoft Office suite of
tools; Outlook, Word and Excel in particular.</li>
<li>Proficieny with Microsoft Project or a similar
project scheduling software application.</li>
<li>Technical information gathering and analysis
skills.</li>
<li>Strong PC literacy, good overall ICT skills and
appreciation of common hardware and software products.</li>
<li>Internet proficiency and cyber security
aware.<strong><br /></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Education and
Experience</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Experience/knowledge of project management
techniques and methods; knowledge and application of Project Management methodologies and
techniques.</li>
<li>Experience of bid management.</li>
<li>Basic knowledge of ATC environment is desirable
but not essential.</li>
<li>Experience of (project based) personnel
management.</li>
<li>Experience in a customer-facing role.</li>
<li>Experience of dealing with internal departments
of mixed disciplines and personnel at all levels.<strong><br /></strong></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>                ]]>
            </description>
            <applyUrl><![CDATA[https://micronav.orangehrmlive.com/recruitmentApply/applyVacancyAdvanced/id/33]]></applyUrl>
            <companyId><![CDATA[131469]]></companyId>


                            <city><![CDATA[Bournemouth]]></city>
                <country><![CDATA[GB]]></country>
            
                            <postalCode><![CDATA[BH5 2HU]]></postalCode>
            
        </job>
            <job>
            <partnerJobId><![CDATA[32]]></partnerJobId>
            <company><![CDATA[Micro Nav]]></company>
            <title><![CDATA[Senior Systems Engineer (Requirements Engineer)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[
                <p><strong></strong></p>
<p><strong>Purpose Of Job</strong><br />As Senior Systems Engineer you will be reporting to the
Head of Quality Assurance and Systems and will be responsible for providing requirements analysis and systems
engineering support for the following business functions:</p>
<p>&bull; Product development for customer projects
and R&amp;D<br />&bull; Sales and
Marketing<br />&bull; Customer
Support</p>
<p>The ideal candidate will be required to
demonstrate versatility (to deal with a wide range of tasks) and flexibility (to deal with rapid changes in
priority). The ability to handle multiple tasks concurrently is essential.<br />The role will be customer facing and you will be expected
to be the focal point for many of the initial and in project customer interactions.</p>
<p><strong>Key Duties &amp;
Responsibilities</strong><br />Ensure accurate
capture of the customer requirements, covering solution architecture, development of new and updated features
and data interfaces to third-party systems.<br />Represent the company during activities with customers, integration partners and end-users
including requirements gathering, critical design reviews and integration activities held either on-site or
via on-line meetings.<br />Ensure customer
requirements are translated into software requirements which:</p>
<p>&bull; Reflect the proposed solution
architecture.<br />&bull; Reflect the
operational needs.<br />&bull; Provide a
suitable platform for software testing.<br />&bull; Will be accepted by the customer first time.</p>
<p>Review solutions to ensure that they address the
corresponding functional requirements and that the proposed solution meets both customer needs and any
identified internal needs.<br />Provide system
level guidance and technical advice, as required, to other departments.<br />Ensure that the requirements baseline for each product is maintained.<br
/>Comply with the requirements of the company Quality
Management System.<br />Maintain awareness of,
and acquire knowledge on, specialist technical topics &ndash; as required &ndash; to support specific project
and internal needs.<br />Own the process
improvement plan in the systems team and related functions of the business.<br />Attend the office in Southbourne three days a week and as
requested.<br />Travel to customer sites, and
be able to travel, across the world.</p>
<p><br /><strong>Technical
Requirements</strong><br />Knowledge of
Systems engineering best practice.<br />Expert
understanding of ATC operational protocols and procedures.<br />Knowledge and use of the Windows family of operating systems.</p>
<p><strong>Education &amp;
Experience</strong><br />Essential:</p>
<ul style="list-style-type: disc;">
<li>Knowledge/experience of engineering practices,
processes, methods, and tools; including requirements engineering and solution architecting.<br />Engaging with internal and external stakeholders at all
levels<br />Deriving of requirements on system
components, to fulfil the high-level customer requirements.<br />Preparing detailed requirements specifications to control the development and testing
of software.<br />Strong PC literacy, good
overall IT skills and appreciation of common hardware and software products.<br />Understanding of requirements management tools.<br
/>Understanding of MS Office tools<br />Experience/knowledge of ATC/ATM environment</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>                ]]>
            </description>
            <applyUrl><![CDATA[https://micronav.orangehrmlive.com/recruitmentApply/applyVacancyAdvanced/id/32]]></applyUrl>
            <companyId><![CDATA[131469]]></companyId>


                            <city><![CDATA[Bournemouth]]></city>
                <country><![CDATA[GB]]></country>
            
                            <postalCode><![CDATA[BH5 2HU]]></postalCode>
            
        </job>
    </source>