<source>
<lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 08:44:54 GMT</lastBuildDate>
<job>
<partnerJobId>116</partnerJobId>
<company>cltn</company>
<title>Level 2 SE</title>
<description>
<p><strong>Purpose of the role</strong></p> <p>To lead the management of designated Customer and internal development projects and communicate project progress to Key Stakeholders and Senior Micro Nav Management in accordance with the requirements of the Project Plan and Contract &amp; To manage Customer project relations throughout the life of the project. To manage and deliver projects to approved schedule and budget and manage bids and tenders across all lines of business.</p> <p><strong>Key Duties and Responsibilities</strong></p> <ul style="list-style-type: disc;"> <li>Act as Bid Manager for Customer bids and to assist in the creation of a fully developed quotation document and fully costed project model.</li> <li>Provide an initial schedule with bid resource estimates to functional heads to enable them to provide accurate, agreed low level schedules in return.</li> <li>Project manage allocated projects to time and budget expectations.</li> <li>Create a Project Plan including task breakdown, schedule and budget.</li> <li>Liaise with the all lines of business to ensure accuracy</li> <li>Maintain the schedule in consultation with the Customer and Micro Nav teams.</li> <li>Measure progress against the Project Plan, Schedule and Budget to update as required.</li> <li>Obtain formal approval within agreed project criteria for any negative variance to project revenue, profit or schedule.</li> <li>Identify project slippages and to develop recovery strategies to allow the planned events to be achieved.</li> <li>Identify and manage all project risks and to provide mitigation plans, if necessary, in conjunction with the Customer, and Micro Nav Management.</li> <li>Keep all stakeholders aware of any changes to the project timescale and to agree remedial actions.</li> </ul> <p>Assist the Financial Controller in the management of financial instruments and the timely issue of invoices against agreed project milestones.</p> <p><em><strong>Technical Requirements</strong></em></p> <li>Proficiency in the Microsoft Office suite of tools; Outlook, Word and Excel in particular.</li> <li>Proficiency with Microsoft Project or a similar project scheduling software application.</li> <li>Technical information gathering and analysis skills.</li> <li>Strong PC literacy, good overall ICT skills and appreciation of common hardware and software products.</li> <li>Internet proficiency and cyber security aware.</li> <p><em><strong>Education and Experience</strong></em></p> <li>Experience/knowledge of project management techniques and methods; knowledge and application of Project Management methodologies and techniques.</li> <li>Experience of bid management.</li> <li>Basic knowledge of ATC environment is desirable but not essential.</li> <li>Experience of (project based) personnel management.</li> <li>Experience in a customer-facing role.</li> <li>Experience of dealing with internal departments of mixed disciplines and personnel at all levels.</li>
</description>
<applyUrl>
https://minijamigara.github.io:443/recruitmentApply/applyVacancyAdvanced/id/116
</applyUrl>
<companyId>456</companyId>
<city>AAAAA</city>
<country>GB</country>
</job>
</source>
